Aiden Wong

Senior Software Engineer

+65323855

@ wongaiden812@gmail.com

☆ https://github.com/aidenwong812

SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with 8+ years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Resultsoriented Web Developer and Al Engineer with a strong background in front-end web development, Al algorithms and models development, and web application development using Al. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full-Stack & Al Developer

GroupBWT

= 2020 - 09/2023 Singapore, Singapore

Managed Web and Al development

- Developed and maintained web applications using React, Svelte, Angular, Diango, Flask, OpenAl and other frameworks.
- Worked extensively on the server-side using Node.js and Django.
- Deployed machine learning models into production and optimize their performance.
- Took lead on several AI/ML projects utilizing TensorFlow and Keras.

AI/ML Engineer

MLTech Soft

= 2017 - 2020 Singapore, Singapore

Apply AI to practical and comprehensive technology solutions

- Managed and directed research and development (R&D) processes to meet the needs of the Al strategy.
- collaborated with an advanced engineering team and executive
- Managed a team in conducting assessments of the Al and automation market and competitor landscape.

Web Developer

JobsDB

iii 2015 - 2017 ♀ Kent Ridge, Singapore

Gained practical experience in back-end and front-end development Designed and developed web applications using React, Vue, Angular,

- Node is and Diango Collaborated with a team of 4 developers, gaining valuable teamwork
- experience and contributing to a 20% increase in team productivity
- Implemented natural language processing(NLP) algorithms for chatbots and voice assistant

EDUCATION

Master's Degree in Software Engineering

National University of Singapore

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering

Singapore Institute of Technology

iii 2010 - 2014 ♀ Dover, Singapore

Singapore, Singapore

SKILLS

Web Development HTML

Typescript Javascript React

CSS

Vue **Angular** Svelte SQL

MongoDB **PostgreSQL** Three.js

Machine Learning TensorFlow

PyTorch OpenAl Git Azure

AWS

STRENGTHS



Communication Skills

During my work, I realized how important it was to use right words to communicate better. Learning this was intuitive to me and it has enabled me to succeed.



Problem Solving

Resolved 95% of software issues within 24 hours of customer complaints.



Leadership

Managed and mentored a team of 5 developers to successfully complete projects on time and within budget.

LANGUAGES

English

Native



Mandarin

Intermediate

